[Music]
jesus
baby catch a charge extra large and
extra hard put this cookie right in your
face swipe your nose like a credit card
hop on top i wanna ride i do a giggle
i'm kinda wild look at my mouth look at
my
[Music]
up like i'm thighs
that's role play i wear the skies i want
you to park that big mad truck right in
this little garage
dream make a stream out in public make
the scene i don't cook i don't clean but
let me tell you i got this ring
[Music]
fishy
my wig make them feel like you're
cheating put them on his knees give him
something to believe in never lost a
fight but i'm looking for a beat in the
food chain i'm the one that eat you if
he ate my eye he's a bottom feeder big d
stand for big demeanor i can make you
buzz before i ever meet you if it don't
hang then he can't bang
[Music]
huh
there's
[Music]